A Guide to the Virginia Room Biography Files, Undated
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Virginia Room Biography Files, Undated
Fairfax County Public Library
15.5 linear feet
The Virginia Room Biography Files consist of 15.5 linear feet and consist of over 1,200 folders on Fairfax County families and individuals. Folders contain news clippings, articles, obituaries, genealogies, photocopies, correspondence, unpublished reports and family histories, and reproductions of historical documents.
Virginia Room - City of Fairfax Regional Library - Fairfax County Public Library
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Files assembled over a period of time by Virginia Room library staff
Historical and Biographical Information
With the establishment of the Virginiana Collection of the Fairfax County Public Library in the mid-1950s, Virginia Room librarians have continuously collected items relating to Fairfax County individuals. The Biography Files consist of two file cabinets of folders arranged alphabetically by the surname of the family or the individual. The files include news clippings, articles, obituaries, genealogies, photocopies, correspondence, unpublished reports and family histories, and copies of historical documents. Occasionally, approximate birth and death dates and occupation for individuals have been included in the folder title. The files act as a starting point for researchers seeking local family history or biographical information on Fairfax County individuals. Library staff is continuously adding to these files.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
None
None
Index Terms
Fairfax County, Virginia
Container List
- Adameuski, James F.
- Adams, Hebron
- Adams, John & Abigail
- Albo, Dave
- Alcorn, Walter L.
- Alden, Robert "Bob", Washington Post editor
- Alexander Family
- Alexander, Joseph, 1930-?
- Alford Family
- Alix, Jack
- Allen, Dorothy
- Allums, John F.
- Almond, James Linsay Jr., 1898-1986
- Anderson, Joy
- Anderson, Peyton, 1838-1914
- Annan Family
- Annunziata, Rosemarie
- Ansley, William
- Archer, Louise A. Reeves, 1893-1948
- Ardis, Barbara M.
- Armel, Vicky O.
- Armentrout Family
- Armstrong, Terry
- Artemel, Janice G., 1942-?
- Asbury Family
- Ashby, John, 1707-1789
- Ashby, R. Barry
- Ashby, Turner
- Atkins, Ollie
- Austell, Theodore III
- Babson, Frederick, BOS, Chairman
- Bach, Bruce F., Judge
- Baggett, Ella, 1910-?
- Baird, Carol Lynn
- Baker, Wallace
- Baliles, Gerald L.
- Ball, Elijah
- Ballard Family
- Barnes Family
- Barrett, Kate Waller, 1855-1925
- Barrett, William E., 1927-1997
- Barron, Robert
- Barry, Stan, Fairfax County Sheriff
- Barry, Warren, E., 1933-?
- Baskin, William M.
- Bates Family
- Beach Family
- Beall, John Ninian Jr.
- Beard, E. Kemper
- Beard, Joseph, 1909-1993
- Beattie, Fountain
- Beauregard Family, GT Beauregard Family. General during Civil War.
- Beckwith, Minnie, 1871-?
- Beerman, John L., BOS, Providence Dist.
- Bell, James D., 1935-?
- Belles, George W.
- Beltrante, Nicholas R.
- Bemiss, Samuel M.
- Benko, Katy
- Bennett, Richard J., 1918-2003
- Berberich, John V.
- Berger, Ernest J.
- Berkley Family
- Berry, J. Owens
- Besley, Florence Eugenia, 1872-?
- Besley, Fred W.
- Besley, Harry E.
- Bethune, John Franklin
- Bethune, Talie
- Beyer, Donald S., 1950-?
- Biderman, Albert
- Birch, Ray
- Birmingham, Irving
- Bissell, Arthur H.
- Blackwell, Homer D.
- Blackwell, Patricia
- Bladen Family
- Blair, Larry
- Blake, Harry
- Blake, John R.
- Blankenship, A. Hugo
- Blankenship, James H.
- Bles, Marcus J., 1904-1986
- Blevins, Lucas, ?-2002
- Blincoe Family
- Bobzien, David
- Boggess, Robert
- Bolton, Eleanor Reed
- Boston, Bernard Norman, 1933-2008
- Boucher-butcher Family
- Bowman, Donald R., ?-2010
- Bowman, Family
- Boxer, Bob B.
- Braddock, Edward, British General
- Bradley, Harriet F., Former Fairfax County Supervisor, 1921-2013
- Brauet, Adelard L, 1909-?
- Brent, Margaret, 1601-1671
- Brittin, Burdick H., ?-1999
- Broadwater Family
- Brocco, Jay
- Brooks, Kathryn, 1906-1996
- Brooks, Lucy Goode, 1819-?
- Brophy, Philip Noel, ?-2004
- Brown Family
- Brown, Jane, 1889-?
- Brown, Mattie Gaskins, 1893-?
- Brown, Paul Edward, ?-1996
- Browning Family
- Broyhill, Joel T., 1919-?
- Broyhill, Lincoln F. "Babe", ?-2008
- Bruin Family
- Bryan, Albert V. Sr., ?-1984
- Bryant, Cunningham C., Gen., U. S. Army; Maj. Gen., D.C. Natl. Guard, 1921-?
- Buchanan, Roy, ?-1988
- Buckly, John
- Buckner Family
- Buckner, Marian E.
- Bulova, Sharon
- Buracker, Carroll D., Chief, Fairfax County Police Department
- Burby, Lillian, First Lady of Sterling Park, 1922-1997
- Burch, Sean
- Burgess, Irene, ?-2003
- Burke Family
- Burkholder, William J., 1929-?
- Burrows, John Lansing, 1814-1893
- Burton, Stephen Douglas
- Bush Family
- Byers, John R.
- Byrd, Harry Flood Jr., 1887-1966
- Byrne, Leslie, 1946-?
- Cacheris, Plato
- Cahill, Mary
- Caldwell, Lucy
- Calhoun, Robert L.
- Callahan, Vincent, 1931-?
- Campbell Family
- Campbell, Lynnwood
- Cannon, Michael D., 1923-?
- Caputo, Carmin C. "Chuck"
- Carey, M. Patricia, Librarian, Fairfax County, ?-1995
- Carlyle Family
- Carne, William Lindsay, Publisher, Fairfax Herald, 1901-1971
- Carpenter, Miles Burkholder, ?-1988
- Carper Family
- Carper Family
- Carrico, Harry L., 1916-?
- Carter Family
- Cary, Hetty, 1836-1892
- Cary, Lott, 1782-?
- Casalaro, Daniel, Author
- Case, Steve
- Castillo, Edmund, Director, PIO
- Castleman, Mary Eloise
- Castleman, Robert Allen
- Castro, Isis
- Cedeno, Charles J.
- Cecchi, Guiseppe, Developer
- Champe, John
- Chapin, Benjamin, ?-1781
- Chapman, Thomas P., Mayor, Fairfax
- Chapman, Thomas P. Jr., Clerk of Court, 1945-67, 1904-1984
- Chichester, Daniel McCarty, 1834-1897
- Chilcott Family
- Childress, John R., ?-2007
- Chisholm Family
- Choate Family
- Christmas, William Whitney, Aeroplane Flight at Fairfax C. H., 1908, 1865-1960
- Cikins, Warren I., Supervisor, Mount Vernon District, 1930-?
- Claggett Family
- Clark, Adele, Artist, Suffragist, ?-1983
- Clark, George Rogers, 1752-?
- Clarke Family
- Clarke, Owen W.
- Clevenger Family
- Clifton Family
- Clinton, William J. "Bill", 1946-?
- Clore Family
- Coates, Leslie R., Chantilly Resident, 1907-1997
- Cobb Family
- Cobb, Mavis, Attorney, 1906-2000
- Cody, Gwen
- Coffer Family
- Cohn, Sherman L.
- Coleman, Beverley Mosby, Admiral, USN; Mosby Descendant., ?-1993
- Coles-Cockrell-Harding Families
- Collins, Sara Jean Dobie, 1929-2014
- Collins, Theodore H. "Ted"
- Colton Family
- Conley, Brian
- Conn Family
- Conn, Marty
- Connell Family
- Conner Family
- Connolly, Gerald E., BOS, Chairman
- Conrad, Thomas Nelson, 1837-1905
- Cook, Ted
- Cooke, Elizabeth Miles
- Cooke, John Esten
- Cooper Family
- Corbalis, James J. Jr., Fairfax County Water Director, ?-2006
- Corbett Family
- Corcoran, Michael (Gen.), Civil War General, died at William Gunnell's house, 1827-1863
- Cosgriff, Chris
- Cotton, Robert Claude Jr., ?-2005
- Counts Family
- Cox, Alice Lee, Librarian, ?-1997
- Cox, Frances, Treasurer, City of Fairfax
- Cox-Phillips Family
- Crater, Flora, Civic Activist; Democrat
- Crawford Family
- Crickenberger, Letha M., ?-2001
- Crippen, Jack, ?-2006
- Crockett, Daisy Juanita, ?-2000
- Croson Family
- Crossfield, A. Scott
- Crouch, Harry
- Crouch, Will
- Crounse, Donald C., Judge
- Crowl Family
- Crozet, Claudious
- Crump Family
- Cuccinelli, Ken
- Curran, Louise, Publisher, Author, 1925-1981
- Curtis, Marshall H.
- Curtis, Mary Lou, ?-1995
- Custis Family
- Dabney, Virginius, Author
- Dale, Jack D., Superintendent, Fairfax County Public Schools
- Dalton, John N.
- Darden, Colgate W. Jr., 1897-1981
- David, Elizabeth
- Davies, Samuel
- Davis Family
- Davis, Jefferson, President, Confederate States of America
- Davis, S. John, 1928-?
- Davis, Thomas M. III, 1949-?
- Dawson Family
- Dawson, Samuel Cooper Jr., 1909-2005
- de la Fe, Frank A.
- de Wilde, Dorothea D., 1916-2000
- Dean, Gladys, 1906-2012
- Dean, Jennie, 1852-1913
- Debell Family
- DeBell, Stuart T., BOS, Centreville Dist.
- Deck, Linton L. Jr., 1929-?
- Deierhoi, Frank L., Judge
- Dempsey, Joel
- Denealle Family
- Denlinger, William "Bill"
- Denton, Richard E., plasma physicist
- Derr, Harry B.
- Devers, Clarence
- Devlin, Suzanne, Interim Chief, Fairfax County Police Department
- Devolites, Jeanne Marie, Va. Senate
- Dial, Rebecca, Author
- Diamonstein, Alan Arnold
- DiAntonio, Mary, 1920-2005
- Dickerson Family
- Dickson, Robert B., ?-2006
- DiGiulian, John P.
- Dillard, J. M., Author
- Dillard, James H. II, 1933-?
- Dillon, Jane Marshall, ?-2000
- Dindlebeck, Grace, ?-1981
- Dineen, Mary Lenore, Architect, ?-2006
- Disney Family
- Dix, Robert B. Jr.
- Dodd Family
- Dodson, Charles
- Domenech, Daniel A., Superintendent, Fairfax County Public Schools
- Donaldson, James
- Donnelly, William, ?-2001
- Donner Family
- Donohoe Family
- Douglas, Henry H., 1906-1989
- Downer, Judith W
- Draeger, Brad
- Drakeford, Richard
- Drummond, Henry
- DuBois, Joan M., BOS, Dranesville Dist.
- DuBois, John H., ?-1933
- Duckworth, Sandra S.
- Dulaney Family
- Dulin Family
- Dumas, Joan Kennedy, ?-2002
- Dunbar Family
- Duncan Family
- Dunn Family
- Dunn, Douglas McClain, ?-2000
- Dupuys Family
- Durham, C. J. S. "Jack", 1905-1991
- Durland, William R. "Bill", 1931-?
- Durrette, Wyatte B. Jr., 1938-?
- DuVal, Clive L. II, 1912-?
- Dye, Robert Randolph, BOS, 1877-1957
- Dykstra, Vergil, President, GMU (1973-1977)
- Eakin, LeRoy, ?-1972
- Eakin, LeRoy Jr., ?-2005
- Eakin, Ruth, ?-2003
- Early, Jubal, 1816-1894
- Easterday Family
- Edsall Family
- Egge, T. Farrell
- Eldridge, Robert
- Elgin, Roger Lee Sr., 1891-1990
- Ellsworth, Elmer, 1837-1861
- Ellsworth, Israel
- Elson, Quin S.
- Engle, Eloise, Author
- English, Brenda, Author
- Ernst, Richard J., President, NVCC (1968-1998)
- Erwin, Harold E., ?-1990
- Eskridge Family
- Estes, Winston M., Author
- Evans, Bayard D.
- Evans, Robert O., 1917-1997
- Everhart, Kathryn M., Owner, Everhart Jeweler's
- Everhart, William "Bill"
- Ewell Family
- Ewell, William Thomas Jr., ?-2006
- Fahey, Helen
- Fahringer, Mary MacNeill
- Fairfax Family
- Fairfax, Bryan, 8th Baron of Cameron, 1736-1802
- Fairfax, George William, 1723-1787
- Fairfax, Joseph Sinclair, Architect, 1842-1916
- Fairfax, Nicholas, 14th Baron of Cameron
- Fairfax, Thomas, 6th Baron of Cameron, 1690-1781
- Fairfax, Thomas, 9th Baron of Cameron, 1762-1846
- Fairfax, Thomas, 3rd Baron of Cameron, 1612-1671
- Falck, Nancy K.
- Falk, Stanley
- Fall Family
- Falwell, Jerry, 1933-2007
- Farley, Carol
- Farley, Guy O. Jr.
- Farr Family
- Farrar, Larston D., Author
- Fasteau, Tybelle L.
- Faulkner, Winthrop, Architect, ?-2004
- Feagan Family
- Ferguson, Hazel Merrill, Librarian, ?-1996
- Ficklin, Eugene D., 1842-1916
- Field, Dawn Stewart, Author
- Fiks, Beatrice
- Fill, Gerald Andrew
- Fink Family
- Fisher, Joseph, 1914-?
- Fisher, Richard Leland
- Fitzpatrick, Johanna L.
- Flakne, Joseph
- Follin Family
- Foote, Frederick
- Ford, C. Vernon, 1871-1922
- Ford, Gerald, Former President
- Ford, West, Former Slave; Founder Gum Springs Community, 1784-1863
- Fortune, George, Engineer; Bridge Builder
- Fox, Ann
- Fox, Maurice W., ?-1968
- Fox, Tom, ?-2006
- Franklin, Jean Schmidt, ?-2004
- Freehill, Joseph H.
- French, Daniel
- French Family
- Frey, John T.
- Friedman, Carol Drake, Centreville Resident; Local Historian
- Fry, Joshua, ?-1754
- Frye, Robert
- Fullerton Family
- Gabrielson, Ira Noel, 1889-1977
- Gallagher, Mary Berelli, Author
- Gallery, Daniel, Admiral, 1901-?
- Gallo, Gary L., Lawyer
- Galt Family
- Gano, John Howard, ?-2003
- Gapp, Frank, ?-2003
- Garbarino, Michael, ?-2006
- Gardenhire, Jacob
- Gardner, Darlene
- Garges, John Henry
- Gartlan, Joseph V. Jr., 1925-2008
- Gasch, Manning, Real Estate Developer
- Geddes, Jean R.
- Gentry Family
- Georgelas, John George, 1917-2007
- Gerard Family
- Gibbs Family
- Gibson Famiy
- Gillingham Family
- Godwin, Mills E. Jr., 1914-?
- Goff/Gough Family
- Going Family
- Goldfard, Lewis & Ruth, Lawsuit re. Lawyers Fees
- Goldsmith, John A.
- Gordon, Guanetta, Author
- Gott, John K., 1929-?
- Granberry Family
- Griffin, Anthony H., 1949-?
- Griffith, Lewis H., Judge
- Grigsby Family
- Grigsby, Alexander S., Slave Trader
- Gross, Penelope A., BOS, Mason Dist.
- Gunnell Family
- Haden, Robin
- Haeringer, Francois
- Haight, Alexander L.
- Haislip Family
- Haley Family
- Haley, Alex
- Hall Family
- Hall, Janet R.
- Hall, Milton Dulaney, 1849-1940
- Halley Family
- Hamel, George
- Hamilton Family
- Hammack, Paul W. Jr.
- Hammer, G. William, Judge
- Hammill, George A., Mayor, City of Fairfax, ?-2003
- Hamner Family
- Hanley, Katherine K.
- Hanlon, Patrick M.
- Hanssen, Robert
- Harbor Family
- Hardter, Frances Williams, Author
- Hargis Family
- Hariot, Thomas, 1560-1621
- Harlow, John W. "Willie", Burke Resident, 1896-1988
- Harman, Doug
- Harper Family
- Harris, Fred, Senator, Oklahoma
- Harris, Herbert E. II, 1926-?
- Harris, Jean L.
- Harris, Kenward
- Harris, Robert E., 1935-?
- Harrison Family
- Harrison, Benjamin
- Harrison, Fairfax
- Harrison, Richard M.
- Harrover, Robert M.
- Harsel, Suzanne F.
- Hart, James R.
- Hart, Nancy, 1846-1913
- Hart, William D.
- Hartwell, Elizabeth, Conservationist, Mason Neck
- Hash Family
- Hatch, Winslow R., McLean Resident; Local Historian, 1908-1980
- Hawkes, Robert, ?-2008
- Hawkins, Eliza Washington, ?-2003
- Hawxhurst Family
- Hayden Family
- Haywood, Verdia
- Hazel, John T. "Til", Developer
- Heath, Gary
- Hedge Family
- Heinbuch, John Conrad "Cooney", 1864-1925
- Heittman, Bob, ?-2004
- Henderson, Edwin B., 1883-1977
- Hennesy Family
- Henry, John
- Henry, Patrick, 1736-1799
- Herbert, Charles Joseph, 1931-2014
- Herbert, Sarah Tracy
- Hereford, John
- Herman, Catherine Winkler, ?-2007
- Herndon, Ellen, 1837-1880
- Herndon, Glasselle
- Herrity, John F. "Jack", BOS, Chairman, 1932-2006
- Hine Family
- Hirst, Omer L., 1914-?
- Hite Family
- Hobbs, Maude
- Hobson Family
- Hobson, Richard
- Holden, Charles Gardner
- Holland, Charles, Tenor
- Holland, J. Sidney
- Hollis, Carl M. "Billy", 1922-1994
- Hollis, Joanne Mellender, 1924-2013
- Holmes, Jay, Author
- Holton, Linwood Abner, 1923-?
- Honesty Family
- Hoofnagle, William H.
- Hopkins, Nancy
- Hopkins, Samuel, 1753-?
- Horan, Robert F., Commonwealths Attorney
- Hornig, Doug, Author
- Houston, Sam, 1793-1863
- Houston, William and Polly
- Howard, T. Brooke, Attorney
- Howell Family
- Howell, Henry, 1921-?
- Howell, Janet D., Va. Senator, 32nd Dist.
- Howley, Dennis C., Author
- Howrey, Edward, ?-1996
- Hubbard, Karetta Browning
- Hubler, George, City Manager, City of Fairfax
- Hudgins, Catherine M., BOS, Hunter Mill Dist.
- Huggins, Wayne
- Hughes, Langston, 1902-1967
- Hugo, Tim
- Humphrey Family
- Humphrey, Robert W., ?-1997
- Hunsberger Family
- Hunt/Huntt Family
- Hunt, Harriet
- Hunter Family
- Hunter, David
- Hurst, Robert W., Judge
- Hutchison, Catherine Ellen, ?-2006
- Hyland, Gerald W.
- Hyman, Rick
- Ingle Family
- Irvine, Frances
- Isman, Warren E., Chief, Fairfax County Fire Dept.
- Jackson Family
- Jackson, James Munson
- Jackson, John, 1924-2002
- Jackson, Luther
- Jackson, Robert R.
- Jackson, Thomas J. "Stonewall", 1823-1863
- Jacobs, Eva Harris, Author
- Jacobs, William, 1737-?
- Jaksh, John
- Jamborsky, Richard J., Judge
- Janney Family
- Jarvis, Anna May
- Jarvis, Kathy, ?-2006
- Jaynes, Julian Clifford, 1854-?
- Jefferson, Thomas, 1743-1826
- Jenkins Family
- Jenkins, Red
- Jennings, Barnard F., Judge, Fairfax County Circuit Court, 1925-?
- Jennings, Daniel, First Surveyor of Fairfax County, ?-1754
- Jennings, Kay, 1921-2010
- Jerman Family
- Jessup, Georgia, Artist
- Jett Family
- Jevtich, Olga
- Jodzies, Florence
- Johnson, Augustus C., Activist; Politician
- Johnson, Constance
- Johnson, George W., President, GMU (1977- ), 1928-?
- Johnson, Michael F., County Archaeologist
- Johnson, William Page II
- Johnston, Mary, Author, 1870-1936
- Jones, Anna E., 1844-?
- Jones, Dorothy Holder, Author
- Jones, Ellen
- Jones, Robin D., Author
- Jones, Sultana
- Jones, Thomas ap Catesby, 1790-1858
- Jones, Virgil Carrington
- Jones, Walter, 1776-1861
- Jones, William Edgar Jr.
- Jorgenson, Harold T., Author
- Jouett, Jack, 1754-1822
- Kaine, Anne Holton
- Kauffman, Thomas Dana, BOS, Lee Dist.
- Keast, Paul
- Keating, Gladys
- Keating, John Richard, Catholic Bishop of Arlington Diocese, 1934-1998
- Keel, Kelsey
- Keenan, Barbara M., Judge
- Keith, James, Judge; Chairman BOS, 1911-2002
- Keith, James, 1734-1824
- Kellam, Revell
- Kellar, Arthur, ?-2007
- Kelley, George J., 1921-?
- Kelley, Robert J.
- Kelso, John B.
- Kendall, Waffendal
- Kennedy, Eleanor Upchurch, ?-2007
- Kennedy, Harold
- Kent, Denton U.
- Kenyon Family
- Kester, Paul and Vaughn
- Khan, Habib
- Khan, Sara Lee "Sallie" Sencindiver, 1930-1997
- Kidwell Family
- Kilmer, Kenton, ?-1995
- Kinchloe Family
- King, George Harrison Sanford, ?-1985
- King, Harold C.
- King, Richard A., ?-2006
- Kinney, David B.
- Kinsman, Jane
- Kirk Family
- Kirkland Family
- Koch, Ronald William
- Krause, Jeffrey
- Kuehling, John M.
- Kuhn, Frank J. Jr.
- Kurylo, Walter
- Kuss, Henry J., ?-1990
- Kutner, Murray, ?-2004
- Lacey, Donald
- Lacy, Elizabeth B., Judge
- Lafayette, James Armistead, Rev. War Spy
- Lafayette, Marquis de, 1757-1834
- Lambert, J. Hamilton, County Executive, 1941-?
- Langstaff, John
- Langston, John Mercer, ?-1897
- Lantzsch, Horst B., ?-1986
- LaRouche, Lyndon H. Jr.
- Larsen, Arnold L. "Larry" Jr., ?-2006
- Lattimore, Harry McLaurine, Lorton Historian; FCPL Staff, 1926-2004
- Lawrence, David & Eleanor, Centreville Residents
- Lawrence, Kenneth A.
- Lawson Family
- Lecos, Mary Anne, Chairman, School Board
- Lederer, Robert, Mayor, City of Fairfax
- Lee Family
- Lee, Earl
- Lee, Robert E., Civil War General, 1807-1870
- Legge Family
- Leidinger, William J., 1940-?
- Leigh Family
- Leigh, Randolph, Orator; Author, 1891-1953
- Leighton, Frances Spatz, Author
- Leslie Family
- Lestina, Dale
- Levy, Charles W. "Levi", ?-2007
- Lewis Family
- Lewis, James, 1756-1849
- Lewis, Oren R., Judge, ?-1983
- Lightfoot, Rosie Mae Crouch, ?-1991
- Lightsey, William Marion
- Ligon Family
- Lilly, George M.
- Lincoln Family
- Lindquist, Donald, Author
- Lindsay Family
- Lippman, Gordon J.
- Lipscomb Family
- Little, Katherine
- Liu, Allen
- Lively, George P.
- Lloyd, John Gilbert, Author
- Loftus, Bernard "Bud"
- Lomask, Milton, Author
- Lonberger Family
- Long, Miriam Storm, ?-1982
- Looney Family
- Loughborough, Randolph M.
- Louk, Ralph G.
- Love Family
- Lovelace, George E.
- Loving Family
- Loving, Gerry A.
- Loving, William H.
- Lusk, Rodney
- Lynch, Edwin W., Developer, 1913-2004
- Machen, Lewis M., ?-1927
- Macintyre, P., Artist
- Mack, J. Hunter, ?-1972
- Mackall Family
- MacLeod, Orrin W., 1936-1994
- Madderra, John Thomas
- Maddox, Ida Mae, ?-1970
- Madison, James and Dolly, 1751-1836
- Magazine, Alan H.
- Majer, Charles E., 1929-?
- Malcolm, George A., ?-1905
- Manger, Thomas J., Chief, Fairfax County Police Department
- Mann, C. Harrison Jr., ?-1977
- Marden, Luis, ?-2003
- Marr, John Quincy, 1st Confederate casualty in the Civil War, 1825-1861
- Mars Family
- Marsh, John O. Jr.
- Marshall, John, 1755-1835
- Marsteller, Frederick A., ?-1980
- Martin Family
- Martin, Hershel, ?-2006
- Martin, Richard B., Catholic priest, 1939-2014
- Mason Family
- Mason, George IV, 1725-1792
- Mason, John, Mayor, City of Fairfax
- Massey, Carleton C., 1901?-?
- Matacia, Louis
- Mathy, Joseph J. "Sunny", ?-2009
- Mattock Family
- Mattox, Bev, Author
- Maxey Family
- Mayer, Alan E.
- McAtee, Kenneth S., Author
- McAuliffe, Terry
- McCaffery, Dan
- McConnell, Elaine N., BOS, Springfield Dist.
- McCormick, Cyrus Hall, 1809-1884
- McCorry, Don A.
- McCoy, Maddy
- McCray, Paul E.
- McCulloch, Mary K., Director, Fx. Co. Public Library
- McDaniel, John B., ?-2002
- McDiarmid, Dorothy S., 1907-1994
- McDowell, Dean
- McEnearney, Virginia "Ginny", 1928-2009
- McGinn Family
- McGrath, Kathleen, ?-2002
- McKee, Robert L., President, NVCC (1965-1968)
- McLean Family
- McLeod, Beth Slater
- McMullan Family
- McNair, Robert Warren, ?-1996
- McPherson Family
- Meadows Family
- Meek, Joshua, 1731-1818
- Meiselman, David I., ?-2014
- Meiser, Robert N.
- Mello, Craig C.
- Melnick, Joseph, ?-2001
- Mendelsohn, Stewart, BOS, Dranesville Dist.
- Mercer, Charles Fenton, U. S. Congressman, 1778-1858
- Mercer, Hugh, 1725?-1777
- Merhige, Robert R. Jr., 1919-?
- Meriwether, David, 1755-1822
- Mershon, Phillip Samuel
- Merton, Allen G.
- Metzger, Evelyn Petersen, ?-2004
- Middleton Family
- Middleton, Thomas J., Judge
- Milberg, Opal
- Millan Family
- Miller, Andrew P., 1932-?
- Miller, Emilie
- Miller, Francis Pickens, ?-1978
- Miller, Harold O.
- Miller, Helen Hill, Author, ?-1995
- Miller, Russell
- Milliken, John C.
- Milton, Hilary, Author
- Mims Family
- Minor Family
- Mintz, Myron J.
- Mitchell, Wiley F.
- Moncure, Dora Wallace
- Money Family
- Monroe, James, 1758-1831
- Montague Family
- Moon, Ilryong
- Moore Family
- Moore, Audrey, 1928-?
- Moore, Claude
- Moore, Mattie
- Moore, Robert Walton, 1867-1940
- Moore, Thomas, 1819-1899
- Moran, James P., U. S. Congress, 11th Dist.
- Morgan Family
- Morgan, Elizabeth, Author
- Morin, Fred C., ?-2005
- Morrill, William A.
- Morris, Lewis D. Sr., Judge, ?-1999
- Morris, Martin E., Judge, ?-1999
- Morris, S. Barry, 1920-?
- Morrissette, Arthur E., 1914-?
- Mosby, John Singleton, 1833-1916
- Moses, Ed
- Moss, William H.
- Mott, James, ?-2003
- Mott, Marguerite H., 1921-2009
- Motter Family
- Moutoux Family
- Moyer, James T., Teacher/Author/Mosby Historian, 1935-1999
- Mulvaney, Richard Joseph, ?-2006
- Munse, Carol, Radio announcer
- Munson Family
- Murnane Family
- Murphy, Hiram, 1830-1903
- Murphy, Peter F. Jr.
- Murtagh, Hugh H., ?-2004
- Mutersbaugh, Jean A., ?-1971
- Myrick, Jean Elizabeth Curning, 1920-2006
- Nasworthy, Frank
- Negrey Family
- Neifert, Marianne, Author
- Nelson, Thomas Jr., 1738-1784
- Nethers Family
- Netherton, Nan, Author; Fairfax County Historian, 1926-2003
- Netherton, Ross, Author; Fairfax County Historian, 1918-?
- Neuhard, Michael, Chief, Fairfax County Fire Dept.
- Newman Family
- Newport, Christopher, Abt 1560-1617
- Newton Family
- Neyhart, Robert J.
- Nickens Family
- Nigh, Omar I., ?-1955
- Norman, Jane T.
- O'Bannon Family
- Obenshein, Richard L., 1935-?
- O'Brien, James K. "Jay"
- O'Dell, Gerald T. "Jerry"
- Odiaga, Carlos E.
- Odin, Dexter S.
- O'Dochartaigh Family
- Odone, Lorenzo
- Oertel, Johannes S., 1823-1909
- Ogburn, Charlton Jr.
- O'Kane, Cornelius J., ?-2009
- O'Keefe, Richard Bennett, ?-2006
- Olin, James, Congressman, VA 6th District
- Oliver Family
- Oliver, George Gilbert, ?-1973
- Oliver, J. Russell, ?-1980
- Oliver, Walter T., ?-1964
- O'Neill, Robert J. Jr.
- Onesty, Catherine B., ?-2003
- Opechancanough, Elder brother of Powhatan, Abt 1544-?
- Ormbsy, Sally, ?-2007
- Ould, James P. Jr.
- Overstreet, Bonaro W., Author
- Owsley Family
- Owsley, Douglas
- Paananen, Eloise and Lauri, Author
- Packard, Jean R., 1923-?
- Painter, Albert L., ?-1958
- Palatiello, John M.
- Palmer, Louise
- Pammel, James D.
- Parker, Mayme
- Parrell, Rick, Musician
- Parris, Stanford E., 1929-?
- Parrish, John E., BOS, Mount Vernon Dist.
- Parrish, Phillip S.
- Patram, William, House Mover
- Patteson, Samuel A.
- Patton Family
- Payne Family
- Peach, Daniel
- Peake Family
- Pease, Ted
- Peck, Julius J., 1829-1907
- Peck, Margaret C.
- Peed, Carl, Sheriff
- Pence Family
- Pendleton, Edmund
- Pendleton, William Nelson, ?-1883
- Pennino, Martha V., BOS, Centreville Dist., 1918-2004
- Penrod, Henry C., 1842-1906
- Perkins, Diane, Author
- Perlik, William Robert, ?-2006
- Perper, Martin H., 1939-?
- Persil, Herbert G.
- Petersen, J. Chapman, Va. House of Delegates
- Peterson, Milton V.
- Pethtel, Ray
- Pettigrew Family
- Pfeiffer, Paul N.
- Phillips Family
- Phillips, Bernard
- Phillips, John, Author
- Phillips, Ruffus C., 1930-?
- Pickett Family